module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What company manufactures the Core 2 Duo processor?', 
    a: 'AMD',
    b: 'Sun Microsystems',
    c: 'Intel',
    d: 'IBM',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: '"Phobos" and "Deimos" are the names of ____:', 
    a: 'Moons',
    b: 'Roman Goddesses',
    c: 'Microscopic Particles',
    d: 'Ancient Egyptian Rulers',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Photosynthesis is carried out in which part of the cell?', 
    a: 'Mitochondria',
    b: 'Centrioles',
    c: 'Chloroplasts',
    d: 'Ribosomes',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'A material that can be pressed into shape without breaking can also be described as:', 
    a: 'Viscous',
    b: 'Malleable',
    c: 'Imperturbable',
    d: 'Insatiable',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'John Adams appears on which denomination of the U.S. dollar?', 
    a: 'None',
    b: '$2',
    c: '$100',
    d: '$5,000',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which animal is endemic to Australia?', 
    a: 'Emu',
    b: 'Alpaca',
    c: 'Llama',
    d: 'Vicuna',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year was YouTube launched?', 
    a: '2004',
    b: '2005',
    c: '2006',
    d: '2007',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The "Joint Photographic Experts Group" is best known for creating ____?', 
    a: 'Photoshop',
    b: 'GIMP',
    c: 'A Digital Image Format',
    d: 'SVG',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'In which state would you find the Great Smoky Mountains?', 
    a: 'Tennessee',
    b: 'California',
    c: 'Utah',
    d: 'Idaho',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is NOT a character from the show "Muppet Babies"?', 
    a: 'Scooter',
    b: 'Frazzle',
    c: 'Skeeter',
    d: 'Bunsen',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];
